LEAH LEBOVITS

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

718-865-7576 <u>leahlebovits01@gmail.com</u> Lakewood, NJ

Goal focused software developer with extensive experience in all phases of business application development. Experienced in communicating and collaborating with cross-functional teams to plan, test and create products. Possesses strong problem-solving skills and meticulous attention to detail, with the ability to quickly grasp new languages and skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- SQL (SQL Server)
- Git
- REST APIs
- C#
- ASP.Net/MVC
- React
- · HTML/CSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript/jQuery
- MAUI
- PowerShell
- Azure DevOps
- Dapper

TOOLS

- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code
- Team Foundation Server
- Microsoft Azure
- Postman
- GitHub
- SQL Server Management Studio

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- · Requirements gathering
- Database design/Relational database management
- Code development
- Critical thinking and analysis
- · Quality assurance
- Strong communication
- Workload prioritization and time management
- Independent and team player
- Ouick learner

EDUCATION

Software Developer Course

CPU Code School

2019 - 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer - Remote

CPU Code Dev - Community Products

March 2022 - Current

- Troubleshooted and resolved SQL issues in a complex existing software system
- Used PowerShell to generate SQL for assessing and manipulating databases
- Performed API testing using Postman
- Tested and modified C# projects such as function apps, and coordinated with team members and product managers to track and rectify errors

BDL COVID-19 Tracker:

July 2020 - March 2022

- Utilized SQL, C#, MVC, jQuery, and Azure function apps, to design and develop the Covid-19 portal for Bio Diagnostic Laboratories Inc.
- Collaborated with teammates to handle the entire stack of tasks in the development cycle within given timelines, creating database schema and stored procedures for UI designing and front-end display development
- Analyzed and refactored the code base, ran clean-up, and added more functionality to the portal for meeting advancement in Covid 19 testing requirements
- Led the training and onboarding of new interns by familiarizing them with the system, providing guidance and evaluating their progress.

Mentor - CPU Code School

January 2021 - Current

- Offered support to CPU Code School students by explaining programming concepts while guiding towards best coding practices.
- Constantly researched languages and expanded skills to help produce up to date session material for students.

PROJECTS

Software Portfolio

Izportfolio.azurewebsites.net

Created data-driven website utilizing a database that stores information about the customized software showcased. This site showcases both windows and web projects created using C#, SQL, CSS, HTML, ASP.Net, JavaScript and jQuery technologies.